Guide to the Samuel P. Hays Post-World War II Radical Movements Publications Collection, 1915-1982 AIS.1981.18
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Radical Right Publications, 1915-1978; III.
  - American Gentile (Chicago, IL: The Right Cause Pub. Co.), v. 2 no. 5, Oct. 1936, 5.
  - American Nationalist (Inglewood, CA), no. 1-65, Dec. 10, 1952-May 1959, 6.
  - American Report: Review of Religion and American Power (New York, NY: Clergy and Laymen Concerned), v. 1, no. 2, 25, Oct. 9, 1970, April 2, 1971; v. 2, no. 6, Nov. 5, 1971; v. 3, no. 1, Oct. 9, 1972, 7.
  - American Southern Africa Review (Washington, DC), v. 3 no. 4-5, Sept.-Dec. 1968; v. 4 no. 1-3, May, 1969-Jan. 1970; v. 5 no. 3, Aug. 1970; v. 6 no. 3, July/Aug. 1971, 8.
  - American Views (Starnberg, Bavaria, Germany), no. 11, April 1940, 9.
  - Americanism Bulletin (Faribault, MN), no. 2-3, June-July 1950; no. 13-21, May 1951-Jan. 1952; no. 53-55, Sept.-Nov. 1954; no. 57, Jan. 1955; no. 67-70, Nov. 1955-Feb. 1956, 10.
  - America's Future (New Rochelle, NY), v. 6 no. 40-41, Oct. 2-9, 1964; v. 7 no. 35-52, Aug.-Dec 1965; v. 8-13, 1966-July 1971; v. 14 no. 1-9, Jan.-March 1972, 11.
  - Anarchy (London, England); no. 98, April 1969; no.100-112, June 1969-June 1970, 12.
  - Answer (Huntington Park, CA: Free Economy Association), 1959, 2nd quarter, 4th quarter; 1960, 1st quarter; 1961, 2nd quarter; 1964, 2nd-3rd quarter; 1965-1970, 13.
  - Anti-Communist: a publication devoted to exposing the Red Menace and Un-American Fifth Column Activities (Oak Park, IL), v. 1, no. 2-3, March 15-April 15, 1947, 14.
  - Armed Citizens News (Medford, OR: National Alliance to Keep and Bear Arms), no. 62, 90, Jan., Nov. 1975, 15.
  - Arlington Defender (Arlington, VA: Arlington Chapter, Defenders of State Sovereignty and Individual Liberties), July-Aug. 1966, 16.
  - Attack (St. Louis, MO), no. 1-2, May 15-July 15, 1950, 17.
  - Attack (Washington, DC: National Alliance), no. 29, Aug. 1974; no. 37, June 1975, 18.
  - Audio Forum Review (Washington, DC), v. 1 no. 5, Autumn 1975, 19.
  - Awake! America for Christ (Burbank, CA), no. 136-139, undated, 20.
  - Aware, the Square Newspaper (Los Angeles, CA), v. 1 no. 1-3, July-Nov. 1969; v. 2 no. 1-2, Jan.-June 1970, 21.
  - Augusta Courier (Augusta, GA), v. 2 no. 1072-1403, May 1968; v. 2 no. 1231, May 31, 1971, 22.
  - Battle Line (Washington, DC: American Conservative Union), v. 1, no. 1-6, 1967; v. 2 no. 1-12, 1968; v. 3 no. 3-11, 1969; v. 4 no. 2-12, 1970; v. 5 no. 1-12, 1971, 23.
  - Battle Line (Detroit, MI), v. 1-3 no. 8, 1968-1970, 24.
  - Asian Outlook (Taipei, Taiwan: Asian Peoples' Anti-Communist League), v. 10-12, 1975-1977; v. 13 no. 1-5, 8-9, 12, Jan.-May, Aug.-Sept., Dec. 1978; v. 14-15, 1979-1980; v. 16 no. 1-4, Jan.-April 1981, 1. (Box 47)
  - Beacon Light (Atascadero, CA), v. 1-5, 7-8 1933-1937, 1939-1940, 1. (Box 48)
  - Beacon Light Herald (Atascadero, CA), v. 33 no. 5/6, May/June 1965, 2.
  - Behind the News (New York, NY: National Economic Council, Inc.), no. 1-4, Jan.-Aug. 1969?; no. 7-10, 1970?, 3.
  - Born's Magazine (Chicago, IL: M. Born & Co.), 1 issue, unnumbered and undated, 4.
  - Break Through (Detroit, MI), Sept.-Oct. 1969, 5.
  - Bulletin Board of the Conservatives (Savannah, GA), Aug. 12, 1966-Nov. 10, 1967, 6.
  - CSA Newsletter (Pineville, LA: Conservative Society of America), v. 5, Aug. 1969; v. 6 no. 1-3, 7-8, Jan.-March, July-Aug. 1971; v. 9 no. 1, Jan. 1973, 7.
  - California Patriot (Santa Ana, CA: Patriotic Party of California), v. 1 no. 7-8, 1967; v. 2 no. 1-3, 1968, 8.
  - California Statesman (San Diego, CA), v. 3 no. 1-27, 1966; v. 5 no. 1-7, 1969; v. 4 no. 1-32, 1967; v. 6 no. 1-11, 1970, 9.
  - Campus Report (Bryn Mawr, PA: Intercollegiate Studies Institute), v. 5 no. 2, Spring 1968, 10.
  - Canadian Intelligence Service (Walter Falls, Ont.), v. 1 no. 1-11, 1951; v. 2-4, 1952-1954; v. 6 no. 9-10, 1956; v. 7 no. 10-11, 1957; v. 8-12, 1958-1962; v. 16, 1966; v. 17 no. 5-12, 1967; v. 18-21, 1968-1972; v. 22, no. 6-9, July-Oct. 1972, 11.
  - Cancer News Journal (San Diego, CA), v. 1, 1966; v. 2 no. 8-11, 1967; v. 3 no. 1-10, 1968; v. 4 no. 1-6, 1969; v. 5, 1970, 12.
  - Capitol Voice (Washington, DC), v. 15 no. 7, July 1, 1966, 13.
  - Cassandra (Pittsburgh, PA: Western Pennsylvania Young Americans for Freedom), v. 2 no. 2, 7, Feb., Aug. 1971, 14.
  - Catholics Concerned (New York, NY), v. 1 no. 1-3, 1967, 15.
  - Cedarville College Bulletin (Cedarville, OH), Aug.1968-Jan.1970, 16.
  - Challenge (Madison, WI: American Council of Christian Laymen), v. 2 no. 2, 1952; v. 3-4, 1953-1955, 17.
  - Challenge to Socialism (Chevy Chase, MD: Shearon Legislative Service), v. 15 no. 14, April 3, 1961; v. 19 no. 17, 20, May 4, May 27, 1965; v. 20 no. 29-30, Aug. 18-Sept. 15, 1966, 18.
  - Chattahoochee River Rat (Atlanta, GA), Bulletin no. 99-101, April-Oct. 1968, 19.
  - China Report (Washington, DC), v. 3 no. 1, Jan./Feb. 1971, 20.
  - Christian Anti-Communism Crusade (Long Beach, CA), Oct. 1964-Sept. 1971, 1. (Box 49)
  - Christian Crusade: The National Christian American Monthly (Tulsa, OK), v. 16 no. 8, 11, Sept., Dec. 1964; v. 17-21 no. 9, 1965-Sept. 1969, 2.
  - Christian Crusade Weekly: A National Christian Weekly Newspaper (Tulsa, OK), v. 9 no. 49-52, Oct. 19-Nov. 9, 1969; v. 10 no. 1-52, Nov. 16, 1969-Nov. 8, 1970; v. 11 no. 1-52, Nov. 15, 1970-Nov. 7, 1971; v. 12 no. 1-52, Nov. 14, 1971-Oct. 29, 1972, 3.
  - Christian Crusade Weekly: A National Christian Weekly Newspaper (Tulsa, OK), v. 13 no. 1-52, Nov. 5, 1972-Nov. 11, 1973; v. 14 no. 1-52, Nov. 18, 1973-Dec 1, 1974; v. 15 no. 1-50, Dec. 8, 1974-Dec. 21, 1975; v. 16 or "18" no. 1-47, Jan. 4, 1976-Jan. 16, 1977; v. 19 no. 1-23, Jan. 23, 1977-Jan. 15, 1978; v. 20 no. 1-6, Jan. 29-April 15, 1978, 1. (Box 50)
  - Christian Defense League Special Report (Baton Rouge, LA), no. 2-3, undated, 2.
  - Christian Economics (New York, NY: Christian Freedom Foundation, Inc.), v. 16 no. 19, Oct. 20, 1964; v. 17 no. 20-24, Nov. 2-Dec. 28, 1965; v. 18 no. 1-24, 1966; v. 19-23, 1967-1971; v. 24 no. 1-4, Jan.-April 1972, 3.
  - Christian Free Press (Glendale, CA: Militant Christian Patriots), no. 17, Feb. 1938, 1. (Box 51)
  - Christian Index (St. Jackson, TN: CME Publishing House), v. 100-103, 1967-1970, 2.
  - Church League of America Special Report (Wheaton, IL), Oct. 1965; May 1966, 3.
  - Cinema Educational Guild (Hollywood, CA), Nov. 1969; Jan., March, May, Sept. 1970; Jan., March, Aug. 1971, 4.
  - Cinema Educational Guild News Bulletin (Hollywood, CA), no. 18, 27, 30-31, 33, 41, 47-50, 52, 55, 57, 61-66, 68, 72-76, 78, 80 85, 87,89, 92 103, 107-108, 122, 134-150, 1951-1970, 5.
  - Citizen (Jackson, MI: The Citizens Council), v. 6-9, 1961/1962-1964/1965; v. 10, no. 9-11, June-Sept. 1966; v. 11-13, 1966/1967-1968/1969; v. 14 no. 1-10, 1969/1970; v. 19 no. 2-11, Nov. 1974-Sept.1975, 6.
  - Citizens Informer (St. Louis, MO), v. 7 no. 9, Oct. 1974, 7.
  - Citizens' Report (Metairie, LA: South Louisiana Citizens' Council, Inc.), v. 8 no. 5-9, May-Dec. 1966; v. 9-12, 1967-1970; v. 13 no. 1-8, Jan. Sept. 1971; v. 14 no. 1-10, Dec. 1971-Dec. 1972; v. 15 no. 1, Jan. 1973, 8.
  - Closer Up (Palm Beach, FL: RAH, Inc.), Yr. 22 no. 12-25, June 17-Dec. 30, 1966; Yr. 23-25, 1967-1969; Yr. 26 no. 1-11, 17-19, 21-26, Jan.-June, Aug.-Dec. 1970, 9.
  - Closer-Ups (Washington, DC: Upton Close), v. 6 no. 3, Feb. 10, 1950; v. 7 no. 1, 8, Jan. 8, May 15, 1951, 10.
  - Combat (New York, NY: Combat Review Inc.), v. 1 no. 1-32, Sept. 1968-Dec. 1969; v. 2 no. 1-24, Jan.-Dec. 1970; v. 3 no. 1-2, Jan. 1971, 11.
  - Commentary on Liberty (Philadelphia, PA), v. 1 no. 1-3, Sept.-Nov. 1965; v. 2-3 1966-1967; v. 4, Jan- Nov. 1968; v. 5, Jan- Aug. 1968; v. 6 no. 1-3, Sept- Dec. 1969, 12.
  - Common Sense (Union, NJ), no. 352, Nov. 1, 1960; no. 366, June 1, 1961; no. 435-605, Sept. 15, 1964-May 15, 1972, 1. (Box 52)
  - Compact (Portland, OR), v. 1 no. 1-2, May 11-June 12, 1967, 2.
  - Congressional Record Digest and Tally of Roll Call Votes (Washington, DC: Americans for Constitutional Action), v. 6 no. 1-7, Feb.-Aug. 1966; v. 7 no. 1-7, Feb.-Dec. 1967; v. 8 no. 1-3, April-Sept. 1968; v. 9 no. 1-2, April-Oct. 1969; v. 10 no. 1, Sept. 1970; v. 11 no. 1-2, May-Nov. 1971; v. 12 no. 2, Sept. 1972, 3.
  - Conservative Journal (New Orleans, LA: Conservative Society of America), v. 1, June 1967 Dec. 1968; v. 2 no. 1-6, Jan.-Sept. 1964, 4.
  - Conservative Society of America (New Orleans, LA), CSA no. 1-27, 1961-1970; CSA no. 72-1 – 72-3, 1972, 5.
  - Constitutional Alliance National Newsletter (Lansing, MI), v. 1 no. 3-8, Jan.-June 1968, 6.
  - Constitution Party Newsletter (Houston, TX), v. 1, no. 1-4, 7-12, March-June, Sept. 1965-Feb. 1966; v. 2, no. 14-15, April-May 1966, 7.
  - Contact (Waco, TX: Contenders), May-June, Sept. 1966, 9.
  - Constitutional Voice (Camp Hill, PA: Constitutional Voice Committee), no. 1-2, Dec. 1967-Feb. 1968, 8.
  - Cotten's Conservative Viewpoint (Bakersfield, CA), v. 3 no. 126, May 22, 1965; v. 3 no. 263-264, Nov. 3-4, 1965; v. 4 no. 32, Aug. 13, 1966; v. 4 no. 39, Sec. 4, Oct. 1, 1966; v. 4 no. 41-46, Oct. 29-Nov. 19, 1966; v. 4 no. 48-52, Dec. 3-21, 1966; v. 5 no. 1-3, 5-8, 10, 23-143, Jan. 7-21, Jan. 28-Feb. 25, March 4-July 29, Aug. 14-Dec. 30, 1967; v. 6 no. 1-11, 13-18, 27-84, Jan. 1-Jan. 8/12, Jan. 15-20, Jan. 31/Feb. 5-April 6, 1968; v. 7 no. 25-52, June 14-Dec. 27, 1969; v. 8 no. 1-26, 30 46, Jan. 8-July 4, 1970, Aug. 1-Nov. 30, 1970; v. 9 no. 1-11, Jan. 15-Dec. 1971; v. 10 no. 1-10, Jan.-Oct. 1972, 10.
  - Councilor (Shreveport, LA: Citizens' Council of Louisiana), v. 1 no. 6, 9, 16, 23, 1963; v. 2 no. 1, 4, 8-24, 1964; v. 3-7 no. 7, 10-11, 1965-July 13, Sept. 14-Oct. 5, 1970, 1. (Box 53)
  - Councilor Newsletter (Homer, LA: Association of Citizens' Councils of Louisiana), v. 1 no. 12, Dec. 1967, 2.
  - Count Down, Faith, Facts and Freedom (Wichita, KS), no. 48-98, Sept. 1966-Nov. 1970, 3.
  - Counterattack (New York, NY: American Business Consultants), v. 21, 1967; v. 23, 1969; v. 24, 1970, 4.
  - Creative Californian (Glendale, CA: Young Americans for Freedom), v. 1 no. 6-8, June-Oct. 1968, 5.
  - Creek County Advisor (Sapulpa, OK), v. 1 no. 1-7, 17-18, 20, 24, 26, 31, May 17, June 29, Sept. 6-13, Sept. 27, Oct. 28, Nov. 8, Dec. 13, 1958; v. 2 no. 1, 17, 21-24, 29-30, 37, 43, Jan. 3, April 25, May 23-June 13, July 18-25, Sept. 19, Oct. 31, 1959; v. 4 no. 8, 13, May 1, Nov. 1961; v. 5 no. 5, May 1962, 6.
  - Cross and the Flag (Glendale, CA; St. Louis, MO: Christian Nationalist Crusade), v. 4 no. 12, March 1946; v. 5 no. 2, May 1946; v. 6 no. 4-6, 8, 10, Aug. 1947-March 1948; v. 7 no. 1-3, 5-6, 8-11, April 1948-March 1949; v. 8, April 1949-March 1950; v. 9, April 1950-March 1951; v. 10, April 1951-March 1952; v. 11, April 1952-March 1953; v. 12, 1953, 7.
  - Cross and the Flag (Glendale, CA; St. Louis, MO: Christian Nationalist Crusade), v. 13-28, 1954-1969; v. 29 no. 1-4, 19, 1970, 1. (Box 54)
  - Cross Fire (Detroit, MI: Greater Detroit Student Anti-Communist Coalition), v. 1 no. 1, Dec. 1969, 1. (Box 55)
  - Dan Smoot Report (Dallas, TX), v. 8-14, 1962-1968, 2.
  - Dart Bulletin (Red Bank, NJ), v. 5 no. 11-12, Sept.-Oct. 1966; v. 6 no. 1-7, 9, Feb.-Sept., Dec. 8, 1967; v. 7 no. 1-4, 6, Jan.-July, Oct. 22, 1968; v. 9 no. 1, March 8, 1970, 3.
  - Dawn, The National Patriotic Tabloid (Portland, IN), v. 11 no. 8-12, Aug.-Dec. 1966; v. 12, 1967; v. 13 no. 1, Jan. 1968, 4.
  - Dearborn Independent, The Ford International Weekly (Dearborn, MI), v. 23, April 21, 1923; v. 24, June 30, 1923; v. 25 no. 29, 38, May 9, July 11, 1925; v. 26 no. 23, March 27, 1926; v. 27, no. 12-14, Jan. 1927, 5.
  - Deutsch-Amerikaner (Chicago, IL: German American National Congress), no. 3-4, March-April, 1978, 6.
  - Documentation (Glendale, CA: Voice of America), June 1966, 7.
  - Dollars and Sense (Washington, DC: National Taxpayers Union),v. 4 no. 6-7, June-July/Aug. 1975, 8.
  - Don Bell Reports (Palm Beach, FL), v. 13 no. 30-53, July 29-Dec. 1966; v. 14, 1967; v. 15-17, 1968-1970; v. 18 no. 1, Jan. 1, 1971, 9.
  - Drumbeat (Los Angeles, CA: California Society, Sons of the Revolution), v. 45, no. 1, 1st quarter 1966, 10.
  - ES, The Week in Spain (Madrid, Spain), no. 349-350, 357, 359, 366, 370-378, 1969-1970, 11.
  - Eagle (Richmond, VA: American Party), v. 1 no. 1, Dec. 1967, 12.
  - Eagle Forum: "The Alternative to Women's Lib." (Alton, IL), Jan.-June 1976; Oct.-Nov. 1977; March-Sept., 1978; 1979-1980; Jan. Feb., July, 1981, 13.
  - Eagle's Eye (Noblesville, IN), v. 1-7, 1963-1969, 14.
  - Economic Council Letter (New York, NY: National Economic Council), no. 628-694, 696-705, 707-711, 713-719, 721-723, Aug. 1, 1966-April 1973, 15.
  - Economic Intelligence Report (Miami, FL: Unidad Revolucionaria Economic Research Bureau (Moviemento Unidad Revolucionaria)), v. 1 no. 1; v. 2 no. 1-12; v. 3 no. 1, all undated, 16.
  - Eddas (Holyoke, MA), v. 1 no. 1, Jan. 1965, 17.
  - Exposé (Cincinnati, OH: Circuit Riders), v. 1-2, 1966-1967, 18.
  - Fact Finder (Tujunga, CA; Phoenix, AR), v. 11 no. 4, Oct. 1951; v. 24 no. 20, Aug. 31, 1966; v. 25 no. 20-21, Sept. 1-16, 1967, 1. (Box 56)
  - Fact Sheet (Los Angeles, CA: Willis E. Stone), v. 1 no. 2, 4, 1957, 2.
  - Facts for Action (Minneapolis, MN: Christian Research, Inc.), v. 2 no. 3-9, Jan. 1964-April 1965; v. 3 no. 1-11, 14-15, May 1965-May 1967, Sept./Oct-Nov./Dec. 1967; v. 4 no. 1, Jan./Feb. 1968; v. 5 no. 9/10, June/Aug. 1969, 3.
  - Facts in Education (Pasadena, CA), v. 1-15, 1952-1967, 4.
  - Family News Digest (Naples, FL), v. 4, no. 1, Nov. 1966, 5.
  - Farmer's Voice (Wooster, OH), v. 2 no. 12, April 1960; v. 3 no. 2, 7, Oct. 1960; Fall, 1963, 6.
  - Fascist, The Organ of Racial Fascism (London: Imperial Fascist League), no. 92-93, 95, 105, 108, 111-112, 1937-1938, 7.
  - Fatherland, Fair Play for Germany and Austria-Hungary (New York, NY), v. 2 no. 25, July 28, 1915; v. 3 no. 5, 8, 13-14, Sept. 8, 29, Nov. 3-10, 1915; v. 4 no. 4, 15, 26, March 1, May 17, Aug. 2, 1916; v. 5 no. 25-26, Jan. 24-31, 1917, 8.
  - Viereck's, The American Weekly (New York, NY), v. 6 no. 5, March 7, 1917; v. 7 no. 25, Jan. 23, 1918; v. 10 no. 5, July, 1919, 9.
  - Federationist, Labor's Paper (New Orleans, LA), v. 48, no. 11-12, May-June 1966; v. 49, no. 1-2, July-Aug. 1966, 10.
  - First Principles in Morality and Economics (South Holland, IL: Libertarian Press), v. 5 no. 9, Sept. 1959, 11.
  - Florence Fowler Lyons Reports on UNESCO (Montrose, CA), Sept. 1959/Dec. 1960; 1961-1963; v. 5, no. 1-8, Jan.-Dec. 1964; v. 6, no. 5-9, July-Dec. 1965; v. 7, no. 1-5, Jan.-Sept. 1966, 12.
  - Focus (Stockton, CA), v. 4 no. 11-12, July-Aug. 1966; v. 5 no. 1-2, 4-6, Oct.-Nov. 1966, Jan.-Feb. 1967, 13.
  - Footprints of Time (Iberia, MO), v. 26, no. 5-6, May-June 1966, 14.
  - Forum (St. Paul, MN: Wanderer Press), v. 1 no. 1, Aug., 1965, 15.
  - Folk: A Monthly Study of People and Culture (Coventry, England), v. 8 no. 1, July 1963, 16.
  - Franklin Letter: A political public relations advisory service (Sherborn, MA), v. 1- v. 2 no. 11, Oct. 10, 1966-Nov. 1967, 17.
  - Free American (New York, NY), no. 1-4, Aug. 1975-Feb. 1976, 18.
  - Free China Weekly (Taipei, Taiwan), v. 5 no. 20-26, July 10, 1966-Aug. 21, 1966; v. 6, 1966/1967; v. 7 no. 1-26, Aug. 1967-Feb. 1968; v. 8 no. 1-26, Feb. 25, 1968-Aug. 18, 1968; v. 9, 1968/1969; v. 10 no. 1-19, Aug. 24, 1969-Dec. 28, 1969; v. 11, 1970; v. 12 no. 1-51, 1971; v. 13, 1972; v. 14 no. 1-51, 1973; v. 15 no. 1-51, 1974; v. 16 no. 1-40, Jan.- Oct. 12, 1975, 19.
  - Free Enterpriser (Little Rock, AR), v. 18 no. 3, April/June 1966, 20.
  - Freedom File (Fort Worth, TX: Freedom Research), Aug. 1966, 1. (Box 57)
  - Freedom Magazine (Los Angeles, CA: Liberty Amendment Committee of the USA), v. 11 no. 3-6, May-Dec. 1966; v. 12-16 no. 2, 1967-Summer 1971, 2.
  - Freedom Press: Your Independent Free Enterprise News (Glendale, CA), v. 5 no. 1-24, 1965; v. 6 no. 1-24, 1966; v. 7 no. 1-29, 1967, 3.
  - Freedom's Facts (Washington, DC: All American Conference), v. 14 no. 9-12, Sept.-Dec. 1966; v. 15, 1967; v. 16, 1968; v. 17 no. 1, 5-9, 11-12, Jan., May-Sept., Nov.-Dec., 1969; v. 18 no. 1-5, Jan.-May 1970, 4.
  - Freedom's Voice (Camp Lake, WI), 1964, 5.
  - Freeman: A Fortnightly for Individualists (Orange, CT), v. 1, 1951; v. 3 no. 1-26, Oct. 6, 1952-Sept. 21, 1953; v. 4 no. 2-20, Oct. 19, 1953-June 28, 1954; v. 5 no. 1-17, July 1954-Nov. 1955, 6.
  - Freeman (Irvington on Hudson, NY: Foundation for Economic Education), v. 9 no. 10-12, 1959; v. 10 no. 1-7, Jan.-July, 1960; v. 16 no. 6, 11-12, June, Nov.-Dec., 1966; v. 17, 1967, 7.
  - Freeman (Irvington on Hudson, NY: Foundation for Economic Education), v. 18-20, 1968-1970; v. 21 no. 2, Feb. 1971, 1. (Box 58)
  - Friends of the Schools News (Belvidere, SD: Friends of the South Dakota Schools Association), v. 10, no. 3, Sept. 1965; v. 11, no. 1-3, May-Sept. 1966, 2.
  - Georgia Tribune (Columbus, GA), v. 27 no. 42, Oct. 6, 1960, 3.
  - Good News Broadcaster (Lincoln, NE), Sept. 1968, 4.
  - Grace and Race: The Kingdom Message (Farmington, NM), v. 1 no. 1, 3, Oct.- Nov. 1966, 5.
  - Grass Roots: An Independent Monthly Journal Dedicated to a Scientific Study of the Trends (San Angelo, TX), v. 9 no. 97, Aug. 1960; v. 15 no. 172-180, Sept. 1966-May 1967; v. 16 no. 181-192, June 1967-May 1968; v. 17 no. 193-204, June 1968-May 1969; v. 18 no. 205-208, June 1969-Feb. 1970, 6.
  - Greater Nebraskan (Omaha, NE: The Congress of Freedom), v. 38, Autumn, 1961; v. 42-44, 1965-1967, 7.
  - Greek Report (Washington, DC: Young Americans for Freedom), v. 12 no. 3, June 1966, 8.
  - Hilaire du Berrier Report (Paris, France), May 20, 1958; v. 3 no. 8-10, Jan.-April 1961; v. 4 no. 2-11, May 1961-March 1962; v. 5-12, April 1962-March 1970; v. 13 no. 1-5, April-Sept. 1970, 9.
  - Harvard Conservative (Cambridge, MA: Charles River Literary Society, Harvard College), v. 3 no. 2-4, Dec. 1964-May 1968, 10.
  - Headlines and What's Behind Them (New York, NY), v. 3 no. 4, 6-9, March 15-Dec. 31, 1951; v. 4 no. 5, Oct. 10, 1952; v. 6 no. 1, April 5, 1954; v. 7 no. 1, April 5, 1955, 11.
  - Herald of Freedom and Metropolitan Review (Zarephath, NJ), v. 1, no. 1-13, May 20-Nov. 4, 1966; v. 2, Nov. 18, 1966-May 5, 1967; v. 3, May 19-Nov. 3, 1967; v. 4, Nov. 17, 1967-May 3, 1968; v. 5, May 17-Nov. 1, 1968; v. 6, Nov. 15, 1968-May 2, 1969; v. 7, May 16-Oct. 31, 1969; v. 8, Nov. 14, 1969-May 1, 1970; v. 9, May 15-Oct. 30, 1970; v. 10, Aug. 12, 1966-Jan. 27, 1967; v. 11, Feb. 10-July 28, 1967; v. 12, Aug. 11, 1967-Jan. 26, 1968; v. 13, Feb. 9-July 26, 1968; v. 14, Aug. 9, 1968-Jan. 24, 1969; v. 15, Feb. 7-July 25, 1969; v. 16, Aug. 8, 1969-Jan. 23, 1970; v. 17, Feb. 6-July 24, 1970; v. 18, Aug. 7, 1970-Jan. 22, 1971; v. 19, no. 1-4, Feb. 5-March 19, 1971, 12.
  - Heads Up, "Dedicated to Fight Communism" (Oroville, CA), v. 5 no. 8-10, Aug.-Oct. 1966, 13.
  - Herald of Health, Your Guide to Healthful Living the Natural Way (Lamoni, IA), v. 71 no. 10, Oct. 1966; v. 72 no. 4-12, April-Dec. 1967; v. 73 no. 1-5, Jan.-May 1968, 14.
  - Hudson Letter by Charles B. Hudson (Englewood, CO), Aug.-Nov. 1961; Dec. 1962; 1963-1967; April-Oct. 1968, 15.
  - Houston Tribune (Houston, TX), v. 2 no. 47-52, June 16-July 21 1966; v. 3, July 28, 1966-Sept. 14, 1967; v. 4, Sept. 21, 1967-Sept. 12, 1968; v. 5, Sept. 19, 1968-Sept. 25, 1969; v. 6 no. 1 34, Oct. 2, 1969-May 28, 1970, 1. (Box 59)
  - Houston Tribune (Houston, TX), v. 2 no. 47-52, June 16-July 21 1966; v. 3, July 28, 1966-Sept. 14, 1967; v. 4, Sept. 21, 1967-Sept. 12, 1968; v. 5, Sept. 19, 1968-Sept. 25, 1969; v. 6 no. 1 34, Oct. 2, 1969-May 28, 1970, 1. (Box 60)
  - Human Events (Washington, DC), v. 24 no. 4-52, 1964; v. 25-30 no. 48, 1965-Nov. 28, 1970, 1. (Box 61)
  - Human Events (Washington, DC), v. 24 no. 4-52, 1964; v. 25-30 no. 48, 1965-Nov. 28, 1970 (Box 62)
  - Human Events Pamphlets (Chicago, IL), no. 1-46, Dec. 1946-Sept. 1949, 1. (Box 63)
  - ISI Campus Report (Philadelphia, PA: Intercollegiate Society of Individualists), v. 2 no. 2, Winter 1963/1964, 2.
  - Imua Spotlight (Honolulu, HI: Hawaiian Foundation for American Freedom), v. 17 no. 4-5, June-Oct. 1966, 3.
  - Impact in the News (Los Angeles, CA), v. 8 no. 1-5, Jan.-Aug. 1968, 4.
  - Independent American (New Orleans, LA; Littleton, CO), v. 10 no. 4-6, July-Dec. 1964; v. 11-18 no. 5, 1965-Oct. 1972; v. 19 no. 1, Jan./Feb. 1973, 5.
  - Independent Pennsylvanian (Harrisburg, PA), v. 1 no. 2, March 1969, 6.
  - Individualist (Wichita, KS: Wichita College Center for Independent Education), Feb.-July 1970, Jan.-Feb., 1971, 7.
  - Inform National Reports (Elizabeth, NJ), issue no. 6601, 6608, Jan. 19, Aug. 2, 1966, 8.
  - Inside China Mainland (Taipei, Taiwan: Institute of Current China Studies), Jan., March-Dec, 1979; Jan. 1980-June 1981, 9.
  - Inside Story (Washington, SC: Young Americans for Freedom), v. 1 no. 1, March 1970, 10.
  - Insight and Outlook (Madison, WI), v. 7 no. 1, 4, Sept./Oct. 1964, March/April 1965; v. 9 no. 1, Oct./Nov. 1966, 11.
  - Intelligence Digest (Cheltenham, England), no. 334-338, Sept. 1966-Jan. 1967; no. 340-379, March 1967-June 1970; no. 382-385, Sept.-Dec. 1970; no. 388-389, 391, 393-395, March-April, June, Aug.-Oct. 1971; no. 397-402, Dec. 1971-May 1972, 12.
  - Intercollegiate Review (Philadelphia, PA: Intercollegiate Society of Individualists), v. 1-3, 1965-June, 1967; v. 4 no. 1-3, Dec. 1967-March 1968; v. 5 no. 1-4, Fall 1968-April 1969; v. 6 no. 1-3, Winter 1969/1970-Spring 1970, 13.
  - Intercollegiate Review (Philadelphia, PA: Intercollegiate Society of Individualists), v. 7 no. 1-5, Fall 1970-Summer 1971; v. 8 no. 1-5, Spring 1972-Summer 1973; v. 9 no. 1-3, Winter 1973-Summer 1974; v. 12 no. 1, Fall 1976, 1. (Box 64)
  - International Nazi Fascist, The Organ of Racial Fascism (New York, NY), v. 1 no. 3-9, Nov.? 1962-April 1963, 2.
  - International Peasant Union Bulletin (New York, NY), v. 15, May-Dec. 1965; v. 16, July-Dec. 1966; v. 17-18, 1967-1968; v. 19, June-Dec. 1969; v. 20, 1970, 3.
  - Irish Voice (Chicago, IL), v. 1 no. 39, 43, Jan. 15, Feb. 12, 1916, 4.
  - Israc (London, England: Israeli Revolutionary Action Committee Abroad), no. 1, May 1969, 5.
  - Issues and Events (New York, NY), v. 6 no. 7, 9, Feb. 17, March 3, 1917, 6.
  - Jag (Oelwein, IA: Dr. R. S. Jaggard), v. 1 no. 13, Jan. 13, 1963; v. 4 no. 7, July 24, 1966; v. 5 no. 1, 4, 6-9, Oct. 1966; Feb., June-Sept. 1967; v. 6 no. 1-9, Oct. 1967-Sept. 1968; v. 7 no. 1-11, Oct. 1968-Sept. 1969; v. 8 no. 1-10, Oct. 1969-Aug. 1970; v. 9, Oct. 1970-Sept. 1971; v. 10, Oct. 1971-Sept. 1972; v. 11 no. 1-3, 5-9, Nov. 1972-Jan. 1973, Feb. 23-Aug.19, 1973, 7.
  - Keeping the Record Straight (Glendale, AZ), Feb. Sept. 1966, 8.
  - Keystone Conservative (Philadelphia, PA: Pennsylvania Young Americans for Freedom), Sept. 1967; v. 2 no. 1, March 1971, 9.
  - King's News Letter (Finleyville, PA: Voice of the Nazarene), June 1971, 10.
  - Laissez-Faire Review (New York, NY), March/April 1975, 11.
  - Free Cuba News (Miami, FL: Citizens Committee for a Free Cuba), v. 3 no. 13, Oct. 4, 1965, 12.
  - Latin America Report (Miami, FL: Citizens Committee for a Free Cuba), v. 3 no. 15-24, Oct. 20-Dec. 22, 1965; v. 4 no. 1-17, 19-20, Jan. 10-Aug. 22, Sept. 19-Oct. 10, 1966; v. 5-6, 1967-1968; v. 7 no. 1-6, 9-12, Jan.-June, Sept.-Dec., 1969; v. 8, 1970; v. 9 no. 1-6, 8-12, Jan.-June, Aug.-Dec.1971, 13.
  - Left and Right (New York, NY), v. 3 no. 3, Autumn 1967, 14.
  - Lewis Bruce Report, A specialized bi weekly digest and analysis of leftist activities (Washington, DC), v. 1 no. 1-14, May 30-Nov. 28, 1966, 15.
  - Liberation (Asheville, NC: The League for the Liberation), v. 2 no. 12, Feb. 1932; v. 5 no. 13, 19-20, 22-23, 26, Nov. 18, 1933-Feb. 17 1934; v. 6 no. 2-3, 6 March 3-31, 1934, 16.
  - Libertarian (Wenonah, NJ), v. 4 no. 10-12, Aug.-Oct. 1969; v. 5 no. 1-9, Nov. 1969-July 1970, 17.